(Leonard:)I'm pretty sure I never said that.
(Penny:)No, you did better than that.
You helped me see it on my own.
Oh, good for me.
(Leonard:)- Where are you going?
- I'm going over to Mike's.
(Penny:)- Leonard, thank you so much.
- Oh, sure.
(Leonard:)Huh.
(Leonard:)Maybe I am her gay friend.
(Sheldon:)Howard, I'm going
to need another Mandarin lesson.
(Sheldon:)I obviously didn't make my point
with those people.
(Howard:)For God's sake,
if you don't like tangerine chicken...
...don't order tangerine chicken.
(Sheldon:)I like tangerine chicken.
I'm just not getting tangerine chicken.
- Can we please change the subject?
- Sure.
(Raj:)Tell us again how you screwed up and got
Penny back together with her old boyfriend.
(Leonard:)Just roll the dice.